Guide to the Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
- Series 3. Concert Programs, 1878-[ongoing]
  - General Concerts
    - October 19, 2002: Wesleyan University Orchestra Open Rehearsal 10/19/02, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Angel Gil-Ordonez (Box 7)
    - October 25, 2002: Stacy Phillips: The Art of the Slide Guitar, performed by Stacy Phillips, Paul Howard, David Chevan, Baba David Coleman, Mixashawn, Noah Baerman (Box 7)
    - November 2, 2002: Maya Beiser & Anthony de Mare, performed by Maya Beiser, Anthony de Mare (Box 7)
    - November 5, 2002: Sitar Virtuoso Chandrakant Sardeshmukh, performed by Chandrakant Sardeshmukh, Ray Spiegel (Box 7)
    - November 10, 2002: Piano Sundays: Rebecca Raffelli and Tom Martin, performed by Rebecca Raffelli, Tom Martin (Box 7)
    - November 16-23, 2002: Echoes of the Earth, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - January 25, 2003: The Bill Frisell Trio with Kenny Wollesen & Tony Scherr, performed by Bill Frisell, Kenny Wollesen, Tony Scherr (Box 7)
    - February 1, 2003: Dragon vs. Eagle Fred Ho and the Afro Asian Music Ensemble with Martial Artists, performed by Fred Ho, Wesley Brown, Adam Colucci, Royal Hartigan, Warren Smith, Michael Weisberger, et al. (Box 7)
    - February 7, 2003: New Works [No Longer] In Progress [Except for One], performed by Various (Box 7)
    - February 9, 2003: Piano Sundays: Marcel Worms: New Blues for Piano, performed by Marcel Worms (Box 7)
    - October 7-9, 2005: Navaratri Festival 2005, performed by Various (Box 7)